谢谢你们准备了这一切.
Thank you guys for having us over.
-这是为可爱的夫妻准备的. -我不知道
- Yeah,this is fun,couples night. - I don't know why we don't hang out..
-为什么我们不多来几次这样的聚会. -也许是因为每次我们吃饭
- with married couples more often. - Because every time we do..
你总是开玩笑，把他们吓跑了.
you make jokes about swinging and scare them away.
你是指那对葡萄牙夫妇？ 好象你没有做过一样.
You mean that Portuguese couple? Yeah,like you wouldn't have done it.
嗨，大伙. 我有个好消息.
Hey,you guys,I have great news.
-罗斯. 我们似乎还在吃饭. -呃..我已经吃过了，不过...好吧.
- We're kind of in the middle of dinner. - Oh,well,I already ate,but sure.
猜猜今天工作上发生了什么?
Guess what happened at work today.
一只恐龙在一百万年前死了？
A dinosaur died a million years ago?
应该是6千5百万年前。请闭嘴~~
Try 65 million years ago. And then try:
我的工作续约考察会议今天开了 我听说进展得不错.
My tenure review board met today,and I hear it's looking really good.
你知道这在学院圈子里意味着什么吗,
Yeah,do you have any idea what this means in academic circles?
我可以留下来了.
I am gonna get laid.
-嘿，大伙. -嘿
- Hi,you guys. - Hey.
意大利风味
Oh,Italian.
没人想歇一下吗?
No one.. No one wanted seconds,right?
不，不，我很好.
No,I'm good.
嘿，你们一定不相信? 猎头给我打了电话
Guys,you're never gonna believe it. This headhunter called me.
说古奇（Gucci）要和我面试. 古奇会聘用我!
I have a meeting tomorrow with Gucci. Gucci wants me.
-我可以续约了. -祝贺你.
- I'm up for tenure. - Congratulations.
你也是. 真巧!
You too. What are the odds?
猜发生了什么?
Guess what?
我终于把那个核从我的牙齿里弄出来了.
I finally got that seed out of my teeth.
我真不知道我最该为谁感到高兴?
I don't know who I'm happiest for.
我知道. 他一整天都在弄它!
I do. He's been working on that all day.
康斯薇拉公主
The.One.With.Princess.Consuela
嘿，莫妮卡,把你的名字改成盖勒・宾奇怪吗?
Hey,Mon,was it weird changing your name to Geller Bing?
不，不. 感觉这样也挺好.
No. No,it felt nice to acknowledge this.
-你打算在哪里办? - 呃..
- Where'd you go to do it? - The..
姓名...服务
The Ministry of Names..
事务所..
Bureau.
你没有改!
You never did it.
我很抱歉. 只是一个变成正式的
I'm sorry. It's just the idea of..
宾的想法…….
Of being an official Bing.
嘿! 我得让你知道..啊..
Hey,I will have you know that..
我真是在开玩笑. 就让孩子叫盖勒吧 让宾随着我到死.
Who am I kidding? Let's call the kid Geller and let Bing die with me.
-给你 -谢谢
- Here you go. - Thanks.
亲爱的,你想要我随你的名字吗?
Honey,would you want me to take your name?
你决定吧. 这是你的名字. 你有特权.
Oh,it's up to you. It's your name. You've gotta live with it.
-让我想想.叫我汉尼根夫人. -汉尼根 夫人?
- Let's see. Call me Mrs. Hannigan. - Mrs. Hannigan?
什么? 你不觉得我的名字在什么东西的当中吗?
Can't you see I'm in the middle of something?
我喜欢.
I like it.
-嘿，大伙! -嘿，乔伊
- Hey,guys. - Hey,Joe.
我们还有些事要做，我们要去看新房子. 你想和我们一起去吗?
We got things to check out at the new house. You want to come?
-不,谢了. -我们搬家你不高兴
- No,thank you. - You're not happy about us moving..
但你是唯一没有看过我们新房子的人.
but you're the only one who hasn't seen the house.
是啊. 和我们一起去吧,你会知道那离城很近.
Yeah,come with us. You'll see how close it is.
不,才不近. 你说它在“契约”里.
No,it's not close. You said it was in escrow.
我在地图上都找不到那地方.
I couldn't even find that on the map.
不，乔伊 契约是..
No,Joey. Escrow is..
有钱,而且...
There's money,and..
却不是银行
It's not the bank exactly.
我不知道它是什么
I don't know what it is.
乔伊,求你来吧. 你对我们真的很重要.
Joey,please come. It would mean so much to us.
知道吗,你们是我的朋友. 我会支持.
You know what? You are my friends. I want to be supportive.
我会和你们一起去的,决定了！
I will come with you. Shotgun.
太好了.
Damn it.
一会见. 我们在11点接你.
See you guys later. We'll pick you up at 11.
-真高兴你能来. -好
- So glad you're coming. - All right.
-真不错. 你够成熟了. -什么? 不. 我去那所破房子
- Good for you. That was really mature. - What? The only reason I'm going..
唯一的原因是我能说出里面所有的缺点
to their stupid house is to point out everything wrong with it..
让他们不要住进去. 我要他们留在这里.
so they don't move. I'm gonna make them stay here.
你的成熟太奇怪了.
You're a strange kind of grownup.
乔伊,你不能让别人做他们不愿做的事.
Joey,you can't make someone do something they don't want to do.
相信我,有些事我想让麦克在床上做 但他....
Believe me. There's something I've been trying to get Mike to do in bed,and..
-我们现在不谈那个好吗 -好吧，假正经
- Can we not talk about that now? - All right. Prude.
听着. 莫妮卡和钱德真的很喜欢那所房子.
Look,Monica and Chandler really love this house.
你不应该说服他们住在这里。
You are not gonna talk them into staying here.
嘿，我能说服人们做任何事情
Hey,I can convince people to do anything,you know?
我打赌我能让麦克做那事. 那是什么?
I bet I could even get Mike to do that thing. What is it?
我才不要帮你做那个!
I am not gonna help you do that!
哦，我的天
Oh,my God.
嗨，我来见古奇的坎贝尔先生
Hi. I'm here to see Mr. Campbell,with Gucci.
这个位子也许就是在古奇名下预定的.
The reservation's probably under Gucci.
拼起来像"拜火教徒"(Gukki)，也许会弄错!
It's spelled like "gucky," which can be confusing.
坎贝尔先生现在还没到. 让我把你带到他的位子.
Mr. Campbell's not here yet. Let me show you to his table.
哦， 我的天. 那是我的老板. 你必须把位子安排在别处.
Oh,my God. That's my boss. You have to seat us somewhere else.
我很抱歉. 这一直是坎贝尔先生的桌子.
I'm sorry,that's always Mr. Campbell's table.
但我的老板不能在这看到我. 我在面试另一个工作.
But my boss cannot see me. I'm interviewing for another job.
我知道,面试"拜火教徒"(Gukki).
I know. With "gucky."
- 瑞秋 - 我在约会
- Rachel? - I'm on a date.
太好了.
That's great.
是啊. 这是艰苦的单身母亲的工作啊
Yeah,it is. Yeah,you know,it's tough. Single mom. Career.
你必须脱离苦海.
You gotta get out there.
呃，你很有精力.
Well,you've got a good energy.
-瑞秋？ - 是的
- Rachel? - Yes,hi.
- 詹姆斯・坎贝尔 - 嗨
- James Campbell. - Hi.
-抱歉. -请坐
- Excuse us. - Please.
他很可爱.
He's cute.
谢谢,JewHunks.com（约会网站）,是吧?
Thank you,JewHunks.com,huh?
所以.
So..
你的简历很好.
your resume is quite impressive.
我的简历..
My resume?
我不会把我的私人约会文件称做简历.
I wouldn't.. I wouldn't call my online dating profile a resume.
约会简历?不,我是说..我是说工作简历
Dating profile? No,I'm.. I'm talking about the work resume.
不论发生什么,就只是毫无理由得唱歌.
Whatever happened to just singing for no reason?
也许别人觉得奇怪.
Maybe people found it weird.
那么
So..
-你为什么想离开罗夫罗兰? -什么?
- Why do you want to leave Ralph Lauren? - What?
-我，我没有. -你没有?
- I don't. - You don't?
不. 我喜欢那里.
No,I love.. I love it there.
如果你不想离开,为什么我们在这里吃午饭呢?
Well,if you don't want to leave,why are we having this lunch?
那是我的老板
That's my boss
什么?
What?
那是我的老板
That's my boss
那是Hugo Boss(著名品牌)?
That's Hugo Boss?
我觉得她想告诉你的是我是她老板
I believe what she's trying to tell you is that I'm her boss.
鲍斯（音同老板）先生.
Mr. Boss..
见到你很高兴
it is a pleasure to meet you.
这个地方太令人伤心了.  如果我在这里工作，我会自杀的.
This place is so depressing. If I had to work here,I'd kill myself.
显然你不会.
But you obviously haven't.
-我能帮你吗? -我想要改我的名字.
- How can I help you? - I need to change my name,please.
我想改掉它因为我在逃避法律的制裁.
See,I need to change it because I'm hiding from the law.
你很好.
You're fun.
-请填一下这个表格. -好
- You need to fill out this form. - Okay. Well,just so I know..
我只是不知道应该怎么做 看，我叫布菲
I don't know how it works. My name is Buffay..
我丈夫叫汉尼根
and my husband's name is Hannigan.
那么应该是布菲.汉尼根 还是汉尼根.布菲?
So is it supposed to be "Buffay-Hannigan" or "Hannigan-Buffay"?
-你想什么就是什么 -任何名字? .
- It can be anything you want. - Well,not anything.
是..任何
Yeah. Anything.
哦..那需要花些时间.
Oh,this could take a while.
-站到一边去. - 好
- Get out of my line. - Okay.
- 嘿 - 嘿,菲比
- Hey. - Hey,Phoebe.
不再是了. 我今天改了我的名字.
Oh,not anymore. I changed it today.
-抱歉.  汉尼根夫人. -又错了.
- Oh,I'm sorry,Mrs. Hannigan. - Wrong again.
显然你能改成任何你想要的名字 所以我想..
Apparently,you can change it to anything.
这是发挥想象力的好机会.
So I thought,"All right,here's an opportunity to be creative."
所以来见过康斯薇拉・巴娜娜・哈莫克（意为香蕉吊床）公主.
So meet Princess Consuela Bananahammock.
那是我想给我们宝宝的名字.
That's what we were gonna name the baby.
- 菲比 - 康斯薇拉公主.
- Phoebe. - Princess Consuela.
你真的把你的名字改成那个了?
You seriously changed your name to that?
好吧. 从今往后我们得叫你康斯薇拉公主了.
Okay,so from now on,we have to call you Princess Consuela?
我知道.我想让我的朋友叫我瓦莱丽（意为强壮的人）.
No,I'm gonna have my friends call me Valerie.
- 嘿，面试如何? -不妙.
- Hey,how did the interview go? - Not good.
你知道吗,面试后我经常有这感觉. 但我打赌肯定比你想得好.
I always feel that way after an interview. I'll bet it went better than you think.
哎,我没有得到古奇的工作， 还丢了罗夫罗兰的工作.
Well,I didn't get the job at Gucci and I got fired from Ralph Lauren.
那面试的确不好.
That is a bad interview.
你在说什么呀?怎么会这样?
What are you talking about? How did this happen?
我老板在同一家餐厅，我在那里面试
My boss was at the same restaurant where I was having my interview..
他听见了一切.
and he heard everything.
后来他把我叫到他的办公室， 告诉我他要解雇我
Later,he calls me into his office and tells me he'll have to let me go..
因为我没有团队意识.
because I'm not a team player.
然后我说“等等，我有团队意识”
And I said,"Wait a minute. Yes,I am."
然后我得在那里坐45分钟
And then I had to sit there for 45 minutes..
而他证明了，事实是这样的.
while he proved that that,in fact,was true.
哦，真抱歉.
Oh,God,I'm so sorry.
嘿
Hey.
这，这是什么?
What..? What's this?
是一瓶香槟! 它为什么在这?
Why,it's a bottle of champagne. Why is this here?
- 罗斯 -我想是
- Ross. - I guess it's here..
因为我得到了续约!
because I got tenure!
-恭喜你. -恭喜你.
- Congratulations. - Congratulations.
这是我职业生涯中最伟大的一天.
This is the single greatest day of my professional career.
- 甘瑟,6个杯子. - 6个?
- Gunther. Six glasses. - Six?
-你要我也喝? -我以为乔伊也在这儿。5个好了
- You want me to join you? - I thought Joey was here. Five is good.
明天我要小心我咖啡里的粘稠物了..
Wow,I'm gonna have a loogey in my coffee tomorrow.
-好吧,我告诉他 -不不,谁也别告诉他
- Okay,I'll tell him. - No. No,nobody tell him.
今晚对他很重要,我不想破坏它
This is a big night for him. I don't wanna spoil it.
- 你确定? - 对,确定
- Are you sure? - Yeah. I'll be fine.
好吧.大家都来一杯怎样?
Okay. Everybody take one,okay?
以色列香槟（比较低档）
Israeli champagne.
还是香草味的
And it's vanilla.
我有了续约，但我没有赢彩票.
I got tenure. I didn't win the lottery.
嘿，瑞秋，你的事怎么了?
Hey,Rach,so how did your thing go?
挺好，但是要几天以后再出结果.
Good. But I won't hear about that for a couple days.
你知道吗,你会得到工作的.我能感觉到.
Oh,you know what,you're gonna get it. I can feel it.
你能吗?
Can you?
好的，为了罗斯
All right,everybody,here's to Ross.
为了几年的艰苦工作终于有了回报.
And to years of hard work finally paying off.
为了懂得你的工作并不意味着什么.
And to knowing that your career doesn't mean everything.
也为了懂得它意味着很多.
But also knowing it means a lot.
更为了多彩丰富的生活.
But more importantly,to full,well-rounded lives.
以工作为中心.
That center around work.
- 为了罗斯 - 为了罗斯
- To Ross. - To Ross.
你知道最棒的是什么吗? 我永远都不会失业.
You know what the best part about this is? I can never be fired.
- 哦，天啊 - 不正经得说.
- Oh,God. - No,seriously.
我有了终生工作保障,你知道.
I have job security for life.
我是说我永远都不会为它而担心.
You know? I mean,I never have to worry.
看看你. 看你多为我高兴.
Oh,look at you. Look how happy you are for me.
不,不是那样，我今天被辞退了
No,it's not that. I got fired today.
而且又没有得到新的工作.
And I didn't get the other job.
瑞秋，很抱歉
Rach,I'm so sorry.
-我觉得自己像个白痴. -不,没什么. 你不知道.
- Great,I feel like an idiot. - No,it's okay. You didn't know.
你们要是给我小小的警告应该会很好.
Little heads-up would've been nice.
谢谢你再让我们看看房子.
Thank you for letting us see the house again.
也谢谢你解释“契约”...
And thank you for explaining to us what escrow means.
我已经忘了你说什么. 但是，谢谢你.
I've already forgotten what you said,but thank you.
想待多久就待多久. 你们看完之后告诉我.
Take as long as you want. Just let me know when you're through.
-很高兴你决定来. -我也是. 这地方真好.
- So glad you decided to come. - Me too. Yeah,this place is great.
真为你们高兴. 尽管你们知道我希望你们会喜欢霉菌
So happy for you guys. Although,you know,I hope you like fungus.
-什么? -霉菌.
- What? - Fungus.
它们在任何地方都有.
Yeah. Place is full of it.
不,才不是. 我们检查过但没有找到
No,it's not. We had an inspection and they didn't find anything.
好吧. 我想我毫无原因地眼睛干燥喉咙痛.
Okay. Then I guess I have dry eyes and a scratchy throat for no reason.
也许是因为你像狗一样把头伸在窗外的缘故.
Maybe it's because you hung your head out the window like a dog..
一路上都伸在外面
the whole ride here.
也许.
Maybe.
那这是客厅? 哦,真暗啊.
So this is the living room,huh? It's pretty dark.
-才不是. -你在开玩笑.
- No,it's not. - Are you kidding?
我想我刚才在角落看到只蝙蝠.
I think I just saw a bat in the corner.
当你的头伸在窗外的时候没有撞到信箱吧?
When your head was hanging out the window,it didn't hit a mailbox,did it?
也许.
Maybe.
我只是觉得你们不买这个房子更好些,
Look,I just think you guys can do better than this house,you know?
或者另一所房子.
Or any other house for that matter.
哦，乔伊
Oh,Joey.
我们知道你觉得不好受但我们
We know you're having a hard time with this,but we..
-真的喜欢这里. -好吧. 好吧.如果你喜欢这所房子
- We love it here. - Fine! If you love this house so much..
你就应该住在这里  我只是希望你们能习惯那种奇怪的声音.
you should live here. Okay? I hope you get used to that weird humming sound.
- 乔伊,我们知道那是你. -不.
- Joey,we know that's you. - No..
不是的.
it's not.
-欢迎回来. --我想你.
- Welcome back. - I missed you.
-哦我也是. -有什么新鲜事?
- Oh,me too. - So,what's new?
我不再是菲比・布菲了
Well,I am no longer Phoebe Buffay.
- 太棒了.你改名字了? -是的.
- That's great. You changed your name? - Yes,I did.
康斯薇拉・巴娜娜・哈莫克公主.
Meet Princess Consuela Bananahammock.
-你在开玩笑? -不.
- You're kidding,right? - Nope.
-你真的那么做了? -对.
- You really did that? - Yep.
你不能那么做.
You can't do that.
为什么？
Why?
为什么？那很好玩 . 很不同. 没有人有那样的名字
Why? It's fun. It's different. No one else has a name like it.
好吧. 我也要改我的名字.
Then I'm gonna change my name.
好. 你要改成什么?
Great. Okay,what are you gonna change it to?
废物.
Crap Bag.
- 麦克废物? -不.没有麦克. 不. 仅仅是废物.
- Mike Crap Bag? - No. No "Mike." No,just "Crap Bag."
第一个字是废 姓是物.
First name: Crap. Last name: Bag.
-你不是认真的吧? -我是认真的.
- You're not serious,right? - Yeah,I'm serious.
很好玩. 那很不同. 没有人用这样的名字.
It's fun,it's different,and no one else has a name like that.
好吧. 如果你喜欢，我就喜欢.
Well,then great. If you love it,I love it.
我的确喜欢 我也喜欢你的名字. 我喜欢康斯薇拉公主.
I do love it. And I love your name. I love Princess Consuela.
我喜欢废物.
And I love Crap.
-你是谁? - 哦，是乔伊
- Who are you? - Oh,hi. I'm Joey.
我愚蠢的朋友要买这所房子，你是谁?
My stupid friends are buying this house. Who are you?
我是麦坎西. 我愚蠢的父母要卖这所房子.
I'm Mackenzie. My stupid parents are selling this house.
我恨我的父母.
I hate my parents.
我恨我的朋友.
I hate my friends.
瞧，我们能做一些事阻止他们.
Look,there's gotta be a way that we can stop this from happening.
比如?
Like what?
你跟我来告诉他们这房子闹鬼.
Okay,you come with me and you tell them that the house is haunted.
你才8岁吗?
What are you,8?
-好吧，你有什么好主意. -我没有好主意
- Okay. Let's hear your great idea. - I don't have any great ideas.
我才8岁.
I am 8.
一定要想一个办法.
There's gotta be a way. I mean,you know..
莫妮卡和钱德搬走了 菲比和麦克结婚了.
if Monica and Chandler move here,and Phoebe's married to Mike..
只剩我和罗斯和瑞秋,你知道意味着什么吗?
that just leaves me and Ross and Rach. You know what I mean?
不太知道.
I really don't.
我能作什么? 我觉得我要失去我的朋友了.
What am I gonna do? I feel like I'm losing my friends.
-我父母说我能交到新的朋友. -好吧,对你而言很容易.
- My parents say I'll make new friends. - Yeah,sure,easy for you.
你比我年轻.我只能自己伤心.
You're young. Me? I'm set in my ways.
那就是我妈妈一直说的: 哭哭啼啼的人始终哭哭啼啼.
This is what my mom was talking about. Whiners are wieners.
好吧.你希望你的朋友开心，是吗?
Look,you want your friends to be happy,right?
是的. 我想是的.
Yeah. Yeah,I guess. Yeah.
搬到这里来会让他们开心的. 你难道不希望他们这样吗?
Well,if moving here is gonna make them happy,don't you want them to do it?
也许.
Yeah. Maybe.
那你就应该让他们走.
Then you've gotta let them go.
我不想承认这个,但你也许
Oh,I hate to admit it,but you're..
是对的.
You're probably right.
你怎么那么会说话?
How'd you get to be so smart?
我读了很多书.
I read a lot.
我以为我们能成为朋友呢，看来是不行了.
Just when I thought we could be friends.
这里,瑞秋. 我刚听说. 我很抱歉.
Oh,hey,Rach. I just heard. I'm so sorry.
哦,谢谢.
Oh,thank you..
还是不知道我的名字,是吗?
You still don't know my name,do you?
现在我不用知道了.
Well,now I don't have to.
罗斯,你怎么那么慢?
Ross,what is taking you so long?
抱歉.我得说它的尺寸不适合搬动.
I'm sorry. It's almost as if this wasn't built for a quick getaway.
瑞秋?
Rachel?
马克? 哦，天呐
Mark? Oh,my God.
-你怎么样? -太好了! 你记得罗斯?
- How have you been? - Fantastic. You remember Ross.
当然.
Sure. Sure.
椅子怎么了?
What's with the chair?
你知道，在地铁上没有座位...
You know,you can't always get a seat on the subway,so..
真聪明.
Clever.
你怎么样?
So how are you?
今天对我来说正巧不是好日子.
You're not catching me on my best day.
整箱的你办公桌里的东西似乎不意味着升职
Yeah,a box full of your desk stuff doesn't say "big promotion."
不,但那很好,你知道. 我要休息一段时间..
No,but it's good. You know,I'm gonna take some time off..
-做一些慈善工作. -你肯定?
- and do charity work. - Are you sure?
我想我们路易斯威登（LV）现在需要人手.
We may have something at Louis Vuitton.
慈善工作，你们有什么?
Screw charity work. What do you got?
我们边吃饭边讨论吧?
Why don't we have dinner and talk?
-我给你打电话. -好吧
- Great. I'll call you. - Okay.
-很高兴见到你. -啊..我有稳定工作.
- Nice to see you again. - Yeah. Yeah. I got tenure.
哦，我的天.
Oh,my God.
看到没有，我告诉你好事会来的.
See? I told you something good would come along.
他看起来真不错.我以前见过他吗?
And he seemed really nice. I've met him before?
罗斯,那是马克.
Ross,that's Mark.
布鲁明戴尔的马克,你嫉妒得发狂.
From Bloomingdale's? You were insanely jealous of him.
-那是马克  - 是啊
- That is Mark? - Yes.
我恨他.
I hate that guy.
不，不. 你不能和他吃饭.
No,no,no. You cannot go to dinner with him.
-什么? 你不希望我有这份工作? -当然. 我肯定他会给你一份工作.
- What? You don't want me to get a job? - Yeah,I'm sure he'll give you a job.
也许让你当他的性伙伴.
Maybe make you his "sex-cretary."
我是认真的. 我只是不相信他
I'm serious. I just don't trust that guy,okay?
罗斯,你知道吗? 好,我们以后再谈. 保安来了.
You know what..? Okay,let's talk about it later. There comes security.
我喜欢这个街道.
Oh,I love this street.
树,大的前院. 那个树桩.
The trees and the big front yards and the actual picket fences.
天呐，那两只狗在做什么!
Man,those two dogs are going at it.
- 嘿. 你到哪里去了? -哦,只是随处走走.
- Hey. Where you been? - Oh,just,you know,looking around.
你知道吗
But you know what?
这房子太棒了.
This house is great.
真的，什么使你改变了?
Really? What changed your mind?
那个住在这里的小姑娘让我觉得好点.
The little girl who lives here made me feel better about the whole thing.
乔伊,以前有小姑娘住在这儿但30年前就死了.
Joey? There was a little girl who lived here,but she died,like,30 years ago.
什么?
What?
我只是在吓你.
I'm just messing with you.
这不好笑. 你知道我害怕小女鬼.
That's not funny. You know I'm afraid of little-girl ghosts.
现在你喜欢这房子了， 你想看看你的房间吗?
Now that you're okay with the house,do you want to go see your room?
什么?
What?
我会有我自己的房间？
I get my own room?
你不会认为我们买了房子却没有给你房间吧?
You don't think we'd buy a house and not have a Joey room,do you?
噢，天呐.
Oh,my God.
我能有个鱼缸吗？加个做爱秋千?
Hey,can I have an aquarium? And a sex swing?
-不. -为什么不行? 我会保持鱼缸干净的.
- No. - Why not? I'll keep the tank clean.
你先请,巴娜娜.哈莫克夫人.
After you,Ms. Bananahammock.
谢谢,废先生.
Thank you,Mr. Bag.
- 哦，你好 瑞塔. -你怎么样?
- Oh,hi,Rita. - How are you?
瑞塔是一个按摩的客户.
Good. Oh,Rita's a massage client.
哦
Yeah.
你为什么不介绍我?
Why don't you introduce me?
瑞塔,这是我的丈夫.
Rita,this is my husband.
我要你告诉她我的名字.
Why don't you tell her my name?
好的，我会的 这是我的丈夫废物.
Okay,I will. This is.. This is my husband,Crap Bag.
废物？
Crap Bag?
如果你需要记得简单点,就把它想象成一包垃圾.
If you need an easy way to remember it,just think of a bag of crap.
- 好的，失陪了. - 好
- Okay. Excuse me. - Yeah.
好吧.你的目的达到了. 你能再做我的麦克.汉尼根吗?
Okay,fine,you made your point. Can you please just be Mike Hannigan again?
除非你还是菲比.布菲
Only if you'll be Phoebe Buffay.
布菲-汉尼根怎么样?
How about..? How about Buffay-Hannigan?
真的?
Really?
是,我是菲比・布菲・汉尼根・巴娜娜・哈莫克
Yeah. I'm Phoebe Buffay-Hannigan-Bananahammock.
你知道巴娜娜.哈莫克是什么吗?
Do you even know what a banana hammock is?
那是个有趣的字.
It's a funny word.
那是一种泳装牌子.
It's a Speedo.
噢，废物
Oh,crap.
- 你在想什么 - 哦…
- What are you thinking about? - Oh,you know.
那两只狗
The two dogs.
- 嘿，瑞秋在吗？ -不.
- Hey,is Rachel here? - Nope.
她还在吃晚饭?
She's still at dinner?
-我想是的.她和谁在一起? - 是马克.
- I guess. Why,who's she with? - That guy,Mark..
布鲁明戴尔的马克. 她认为他只是对她好,
from Bloomingdale's. She thinks he's just being nice to her.
但我知道他想和她睡觉.
But I know he really wants to sleep with her.
已经7年了.
It's seven years ago.
我的时间机器起作用了!
My time machine works.
我们今天在路上碰到他 他说也许他有工作给她
We ran into him on the street today,and he said he might have a job for her.
但我知道他只是想让她接近他的裤子.
But I know he just wants to get into her pants.
那为什么他不想和她睡觉?  我是说她单身而他可爱.
So,what if he wants to sleep with her? I mean,she's single,and he's cute.
什么?
Excuse me?
哦，拜托
Oh,please.
昨天在地铁上
Yesterday,on the subway,you couldn't stop staring..
你不停地盯着一个大胸脯的女人看
at that woman with the big breasts.
像你看到的那样,我在看她的宝宝.
For your information,I was staring at her baby.
我们就要做父母了.
We're about to be parents.
哦，对不起
Oh,sorry.
- 嗨  大伙. - 嗨.
- Hi,you guys. - Hi. So..
-晚饭怎么样? - 噢， 很棒. 马克人真好.
- how was dinner? - Oh,it was great. Mark is so sweet.
哦，是吗，我想知道为什么.  那个聪明的人更可能需要什么?
Oh,yeah? Yeah,I wonder why? What could that smarmy letch possibly want?
哦，罗斯，别这样 他已经结婚了，他的妻子生了双胞胎.
Oh,Ross. Come on. He is happily married. His wife just had twins.
我们该说点什么?
Should we send something?
工作怎么样?
How did the job stuff go?
他给了我一个工作.
He offered me one.
-太棒了! -恭喜你
- That's great. - Congratulations.
我知道那很棒. 那很棒.
I know,it's amazing.
那比我在罗夫罗兰要好得多.
It's amazing. It's so much better than what I had at Ralph Lauren.
-薪水很不错. - 我们
- The money is great. - Can we..?
我们能停一停吗. 是谁说一切都会好起来的,啊？
Can we just stop for a second? Who said something better would come along?
你不相信我. 我告诉你一切都会有起色.
You didn't believe me. I told you everything was gonna work out.
你知道吗,这时候该来一瓶以色列佳酿。
You know what? This calls for a bottle of Israel's finest.
工作在巴黎.
The job is in Paris.
我是说，肥皂剧是很好的机会,
I mean,this soap opera is a great gig..
但，我错过了机会吗?
but am I missing opportunities?
你知道，我总是觉得我自己是个正经的演员.
You know,I've always thought of myself as a serious actor.
我指，我是不是应该尝试更多的独立电影?
Should I be trying to do more independent movies?
我不知道.
I don't know.
你知道吗,我让我的熊听电话.
But you know what? I'm gonna put you on with my bear.
等等.
Hold on.
嘿 小熊,我需要一些事业上的意见.
Hey,Bailey,I need some career advice.